const questions = [
  {
    question: "The interactive web pages and applications are consists of?",
    answers: [
      { text: "<HTML>" },
      { text: "<CSS>" },
      { text: "<Javascript>" },
      { text: "<All of the Above>" },
    ],
    correct: "<All of the above>",
  },
  {
    question:
      "What is the correct syntax for referring to an external script called geek.js?",
    answers: [
      { text: "<script src= 'geek.js'>" },
      { text: "<script href= 'geek.js'>" },
      { text: "<script ref = 'geek.js'>" },
      { text: "<script name= 'geek.js'>" },
    ],
    correct: "<script src= 'geek.js'>",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which of the following is the correct syntax to display GeeksforGeeks in an alert box using JavaScript?",
    answers: [
      { text: "alertbox('GeeksforGeeks')" },
      { text: "msg ('GeeksforGeeks')" },
      { text: "msgbox('GeeksforGeeks')" },
      { text: "alert('GeeksforGeeks')" },
    ],
    correct: "alert('GeeksforGeeks')",
  },
  {
    question: "Which of the following is ot reserved word in JavaScript?",
    answers: [
      { text: "interface" },
      { text: "throws" },
      { text: "program" },
      { text: "short" },
    ],
    correct: "program",
  },
  {
    question:
      "What is the HTML tag under which one can write the JavaScript code?",
    answers: [
      { text: "<javascript>" },
      { text: "<scripted>" },
      { text: "<script>" },
      { text: "<js>" },
    ],
    correct: "<script>",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which of the following function of string object combines the text of two strings and returns a new string?",
    answers: [
      { text: "concat()" },
      { text: "add()" },
      { text: "merge()" },
      { text: "append" },
    ],
    correct: "concat()",
  },
  {
    question: "Which operator is used to assign a value to a variable?",
    answers: [{ text: "-" }, { text: "X" }, { text: "*" }, { text: "=" }],
    correct: "=",
  },
  {
    question: "How to add comments in JavaScript?",
    answers: [
      { text: "//This is a comment" },
      { text: "<!--This is a comment-->" },
      { text: "/*This is a comment*/" },
      { text: "-This is a comment" },
    ],
    correct: "//This is a comment",
  },
  {
    question:
      "What is the syntax for creating a function in JavaSCript named booFunction?",
    answers: [
      { text: "function: = booFunction()" },
      { text: "function+ booFunction()" },
      { text: "function = booFunction()" },
      { text: "function booFunction()" },
    ],
    correct: "function booFunction()",
  },
  {
    question: "How to call a function in JavaScript?",
    answers: [
      { text: "booFunction();" },
      { text: "function call booFunction();" },
      { text: "Function();" },
      { text: "function booFunction()" },
    ],
    correct: "booFunction();",
  },
];
